So, how is NASA planning to launch the
biggest rocket ever to take astronauts
back to the moon after 50 years? Well,
the first step involves filling the
massive fuel and oxygen tanks that feed
the RS25 engines. Step two is the trans
lunar injection, and once that's done,
the upper stage detaches. Next is step
three, where the spacecraft conserves
fuel by doing a slingshot maneuver
around the moon. But, as we know, what
goes up must come down. The return trip
is actually the most dangerous part. The
capsule's heat shield has to withstand
temperatures half as hot as the sun.
Otherwise, the crew won't make it back
alive.
How do you launch NASA most powerful
rocket ever built? This is step one,
Earth departures. The journey begins at